My bedroom...
What the hell did I...
Star in my videos.
If you do, I can make videos
that no one's seen before!
I bet I could reach a million
subscribers in no time!
That's why...
I want you to join me!
In exchange, once we hit a million subs...
Go ahead. Make a meal of me.
Are you all right?
Let's get you to my place.
Here we are.
Oh, you're awake?
Can you stand? And walk?
I'm totally fine!
Hey, there!
That green hair is so sick!
She looks so tasty!
I think I'm about to lose it!
Wanna drink her up so bad, so bad,
so bad, so bad, so bad, so bad!
Ichiko!
Do we have any open rooms—
Fu?
L-Live-sama.
It's awful.
Ichiko-chan reverted to a bat
from blood deprivation!
It's okay, Fu.
Live-sama went off to go find blood for me.
Oh, no! It totally slipped my mind!
Ah! A talking bat!
Whoo
I'll give you blood, so let me
get you on camera later!
Go on. Eat up.
Don't mind if I do!
Chomp!!
Hey, that freakin' hurts!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
That's enough!
I said that's enough!
I'm back in action!
Impressive.
Ichiko!
Why do you get to taste her first?!
You're so angry!
M-Me too!
Hey, me too!
We made a promise.
But Ichiko just got to...
Don't worry.
Huh?
If we hit a million subs for our channel,
you can suck me bone-dry!
I made one hell of a promise!
What now?
Wait, hold on.
Thinking about it, can you even
take videos of vampires?
Or, well, did any of that really happen?
I need water.
What about all this equipment?
Shouldn't we talk it over with Masaki?
I bet she doesn't even need it anymore.
Maybe not.
Garlic Paste
Masaki.
What?
We've decided to move out.
Huh? Wait...
We're pulling out all the
stops to step things up!
Step...
Huh...
See ya.
Starting a Channel!
Good Morning from the Dead of Night!
Live's house <3
Take first crossing
Train station
Is this really the right place?
There's nothing out here.
It's like a nature trail.
Is that it?
Welcome to Banpai Manor!
Once again, I'm Live.
She's Ichiko!
Live-sama's wish is my command!
I'll give it all I've got!
And this is Fu.
I-I...
Fu's a bit shy, but I'll see
to it that she does her part!
I'll do my part.
Nice to meet you.
A-Are you sure about this?
A human finding out about us...
It's fine, it's fine!
I'll make it work somehow!
I-I see.
Now, then—
First, let's get one thing straight!
A million subs, and I suck out
your bone marrow! Okay?!
Bone marrow?
Bone
Dry
Wait, what I said was "bone-dry"...
You don't mind, then?
If I suck you completely dry?!
Completely?!
You don't mind?!
Fine, I get it!
If we hit the goal!
There, you said it!
You totally said it!
Awesome!
Ichiko! Fu!
Devote yourselves for my sake!
Yes!
Yes.
W-Won't hitting a million subs be really hard?
It's fine, it's fine!
Masaki's got it all worked out!
She'll get us there in a flash!
Right, Masaki?
Masaki?
Duh, of course!
We're unstoppable!
We're talking my ideas, plus vampires!
Let's get cracking right away!
I'll do it. I'll get big in no time...
and show those two what's what!
Chu-Chu Girls.
Chu-Chu Pops
While Flying #1
* This video was shot using special
effects. Don't try this at home <3
First, to attract viewer attention,
we'll upload tons of short videos!
Let's see what vampire powers can do,
and try this, that, and everything else!
Hey.
Can you vampires fly faster than this?
Yes, I can fly much faster.
Here I go.
Huh? Hey!
Compared to the Hype-Sis days,
it's a lot harder to get numbers on NewTube now.
Chu-Chu Pops in
High Places #6
Chu-Chu Pops
While Flying #7
Chu-Chu Pops in
High Places #8
Chu-Chu Pops
in Free Fall #9
* This video was shot
using special effects.
Don't try this at home <3
* This video was shot
using special effects.
Don't try this at home <3
* This video was shot
using special effects.
Don't try this at home <3
* This video was shot
using special effects.
Don't try this at home <3
* This video was shot
using special effects.
Don't try this at home <3
* This video was shot
using special effects.
Don't try this at home <3
Chu-Chu Pops
While Jumping #10
Chu-Chu Pops in
High Places #12
Chu-Chu Pops
While Flying #11
Over 100k views?!
Chu-Chu Pops While Jumping #10
81k views
Chu-Chu Pops While Flying #11
100k views
Chu-Chu Pops in High Places #12
3k views
Seriously?
Huh? What's that mean?
Is that good?
It's more than good!
Peach
I love watching your videos. Keep it up!!
Hot Bath
I was so shocked at how much
it looks like you're really flying!
Shiro
I'm totally hooked. Looking forward
to the next one
Rei
I can't tell what's real and what's CG!
Those effects are mind-boggling!
So awesome!!
aa
these videos are so boring,
not even worth watching
Asterisk
Wow, look at you go!!
Peach
I love watching your videos. Keep it up!!
Hot Bath
I was so shocked at how much
it looks like you're really flying!
Shiro
I'm totally hooked. Looking forward
to the next one
Rei
I can't tell what's real and what's CG!
Those effects are mind-boggling!
So awesome!!
aa
these videos are so boring,
not even worth watching
Asterisk
Wow, look at you go!!
I won't let this chance slip away!
We'll keep on trying everything we can!
Chu-Chu Pops
on Top of a Car
* This video was shot using special effects.
Don't try this at home <3
what's the point of the
chu-chu pops lol
Thought this was a graphic
accident video for a second.
Wow! It looks like the car really
drove off! How did they shoot this?
The girl with the pink hair is the one from
that viral short! She's so cool and athletic~
Chu-Chu Pops
But We Turn Into Bats
* This video was shot using special effects.
Don't try this at home <3
Love videos that go all out
making zero sense. Wuv even.
way too elaborate lmao
i was like ???
but it's cute so w/e
Videos with falling and riding things do well
Ideas for places to fall from
Ideas for things to ride on top of
A train would probably make people mad?
I'm not done yet!
Chu-Chu Pops
While Falling From High Up
And after a good number of videos,
utilize analytics right away!
Chu-Chu Pops
While Lifting
Heavy Things #2
Keep on creating and publishing
videos that meet demand!
CG?! Live-Action?! All About the Hot New
Video Channel: Chu-Chu Girls
Chu-Chu Pops
on Top of a Plane
on Top of Mt. Fuji
Chu-Chu Pops on Top of a Car
while Doing Handstands
This could work!
We can totally make it to the top like this!
That hurts!
A Few Days Later
Chu-Chu Girls.
Video Information
Your latest video has been viewed 503,731 times since it was published.
I don't believe it.
In just three weeks?
Maybe I am a genius!
Which means the million-sub mark
is right around the corner!
Masaki-tan, you'll be all mine soon enough!
Where do I start?
Where should I bite you first?
It's too soon for that!
C'mon, let's start our next shoot!
Right-o!
What kind of video are we making today?
Why, now that all eyes are on us,
we'll make our most over-the-top video yet!
Over-the-top?
I would appreciate it if you'd refrain.
Huh? Who?
Shoot!
These childish videos...
end now.
It's been twenty years.
You finally wake up, and here you are,
fraternizing with a human.
Shut up, Shigeyuki.
Don't call me that.
Is she a vampire, too?
Yes.
Yuki-sama and Live-sama are higher
on the vampire hierarchy than us.
P-Please, have some tea.
Thanks.
Here's a fresh supply of blood.
Thank you very much.
I-Isn't it a little soon, though?
I was expecting you next week—
You can never have too much, can you?
Th-That's absolutely true!
It beats running out and having
to go search a hospital like before!
Ichiko!
Well, that hospital turned out
to be abandoned.
Raiding an abandoned hospital for blood?
I don't believe I was ever informed of that.
I see. You were hiding it from me.
Not only did you bring a human here,
you tried to steal their blood?
You're going to make a
big deal over just that?
Still a stickler, I see, Shige—
My name is Yuki!
Just that, you say?
You're flagrantly breaking the rules.
Who cares?
I didn't end up stealing any blood, anyway.
And I was going to tell you
all about Masaki sooner or later.
Tell me, huh?
Even if we were to assume that
was up for discussion...
How exactly do you explain this?
Subscribe
Chu-Chu Girls.
A message from Mother:
Erase the channel,
or you'll be the ones erased.
Actions that reveal our powers to the public
are strictly prohibited above all else.
You've greatly angered Mother.
Understand?
Then be obedient and—
No, hold it right there!
Delete the channel?
You've gotta be kidding!
Thanks to my awesome ideas,
we now have an amazing opportunity!
Masaki!
Stop, Masaki-san!
How dare you, human!
Don't try it, Shige!
Eat this, vampire!
Garlic Paste
D-Damn you...
Did you...
feed me garlic?
Feed me garlic...
Wowie...
Where am I?
To think I was surrounded by flowers!
These tulips get my two lips!
Oh, my!
What's this?
There are pit traps all around me!
Eek!
Trying to humiliate me, I see!
Let's play a game of tag!
So that's what garlic does to them.
I'll be it!
Wait for me!
Okay, now that she's out of the way,
let's get shooting.
Delete the channel.
We can't go against Mother.
Y-You can't be serious!
I would never dream of deleting the—
Delete it right now.
No way!
We're just getting started here!
Please!
I said no!
Delete it!
Looks like those magical
two weeks are over now.
Oh, yeah.
They're not here anymore.
Lily
Such a nice house! I'd love to live there
KitsuOto Girl
Good luck, you two!
no signal
It's so much better now that Masakichi's gone
Strawberry Milk
What a lovely place...! All your hard effort has...
anna
Congrats on the move! A house with two cuties
is guaranteed to be just as cute~
Big Reveal: Our New House
Must be nice.
Boy, making videos sure was fun!
Masaki! Masaki's blood!
This can't be!
FML!
Now I'll never get to suck Masaki's blood!
Farewell, my lovely bone marrow...
No, I can't give up!
How's Masaki holding up?
Is she angry at me?
I don't blame her!
Do I apologize?
Even if I did, would she forgive...
Ugh, there's no way!
Live-sama?
Is your scalp itchy?
Should we change shampoos?
What now?
What can I do?!
Agh, I have no idea!
I have no idea, but...
I want to see Masaki again!
Where are you going?
pandamaru
Masakichi was so annoying. I'm glad she's gone.
Manatee Tears
So did Masakichi end up just running away?
otake3
You know it's over when all the comments on
social media are bashing her.
Show me the Masakichi white knights lol
Yaminabe
the masakichi scandal is so hilarious lmao
all those delicious tears
Chicken Nanban Lunch
Did Masakichi-san apologize on her knees yet??
Wombats Own
This is what happens when you get full of yourself.
#MasakichiScandal
Chappie
cya masakichi
I'm all alone again.
I ended up coming.
I'm so sorry, for real.
Why don't you start by letting me in?
We vampires can't enter a
dwelling unless we're invited.
Then I won't.
Go away. Good-bye.
Wait!
You and I are through.
Leave me alone!
Can I ask you one last thing?
What?
Why do you care so much about making videos?
Huh?
I mean, we had fun making them, too.
But you're like, dead serious about it.
Why?
It's none of your business.
Sure it is!
I want to know all about you!
Tell me! How come?
How come?
Until high school,
I found everything to be a hassle,
so I spent all my time watching videos.
What? Who're you?!
Seriously?
Kikka and Otomi, from your class.
Oh, really?
See ya.
What?
Wait, wait!
Oh, it's fine.
Maybe you think I'm lonely without friends,
but I choose to be all by myself.
We like watching the same videos as you!
I even subscribe to their channel.
They're so good.
We don't know anyone else who watches them.
So we wanted to talk to you.
Really? How long have
you been watching them?
Which videos do you like the most?
Videos were what brought us together.
We became friends and decided
to try making our own videos.
Buying All the Mars Gummies!
By sheer luck, they happened to go viral.
I was so happy.
It felt like we'd found approval
from so many people.
So we made up our minds
to follow in the footsteps of the
NewTubers who brought us together
and set a goal of one million subscribers.
That's the reason I worked so hard.
I never thought I'd end up deleting
the Chu-Chu Girls channel.
It's like there's a higher power
telling me not to make videos—
Why not just make them?
Huh?
Make videos with us again.
We can't let it get out that we're vampires,
but no one said we can't make more videos.
B-But we'll never get good numbers unless...
Teach us how to make videos.
Teach us all there is to know.
And let's make them together.
Starting from scratch.
You've got me to help you now!
Masaki?
You can come in.
You have my invitation.
She's taking so long.
Where could Live-sama have gone?
It's almost morning.
Let's call it a night and go to bed.
I'll wait a little longer.
I'm back!
Live-sama!
And... Masaki?
Ichiko! Fu!
We're gonna make videos again!
What?!
B-But surely Yuki-sama will find out!
It's fine, it's fine.
We won't use any vampire powers this time!
Even then...
Ichiko.
How are you going to pay back
those debts of yours?
If we hit a million subs,
that solves everything.
I-I see now!
Live-sama is putting herself in danger
with these videos for my sake!
All for Masaki's blood.
Understood!
I'll do what I can!
That's the Ichiko I know!
Yes!
You're helping too, Fu.
Sure thing.
Well, I found it fun as well.
Fun, huh?
So?
What do we need to do first?
You're gonna teach us, right?
Okay!
Create an Eagle Account
Step 1: Choose an Eagle Account type
For myself
To manage a business
First, we need to create a channel.
Create an Eagle Account
Last name
First name
Sonoue
Masaki
Might as well make a new
account and log in. There.
Then click on "Create new channel" here...
A new channel name?
Yep.
We can't use the name Chu-Chu Girls anymore.
Any ideas?
A channel name...
How did you come up with
the name Hyped-Up Sisters?
Huh? Us?
In our case...
We thought as a group about
what kind of channel we wanted
and shared our suggestions....
Okay.
Everyone come up with a name!
Right!
Then I suggest Thrills 'n' Kicks, Ready, Go!
No way.
Huh? Why not?!
It's not a kids' channel!
Your turn, Fu!
What?!
I-I think a relaxing-sounding
channel name would be nice.
The 12 a.m. Aged Hyaluronic Acid Channel—
That's a no.
Way too quirky.
It just sounds bad.
What's that even mean?
I quit after all!
Hold your horses!
It's fine, I swear!
I'm sure we'll come up with a good name!
You're up next, Live-sama!
Mayonaka Punch.
We can only go out late at night (mayonaka),
and Masaki got canceled for punching someone,
so Mayonaka Punch!
Mayonaka
Punch
Or MayoPan for short!
MayoPan
MayoPan...
I like it!
Channel name
Create
Mayonaka Punch
Now we've made the channel.
That was super easy!
Next, we prepare our banner
and profile images.
Mayonaka Punch
And now, for the all-important
channel intro video.
MayoPan
I mean, we could shoot it on a smartphone,
but we might as well use
a high-quality camera.
Listen up.
Your intro needs to bring across the
personality of the channel and its members
simply and clearly.
Recording
Good morning from the dead of night!
This is Live, the leader of the bunch!
Chock-full of energy, it's Ichiko!
I-I'm Fu.
Nice to meet you.
U-Um...
Here—
Standby
Now, we import the raw footage
into some video editing software.
I-I'm Fu.
Fu
Live
Ichiko
Nice to meet you.
Here on this channel,
we're going to go all out doing whatever
we want—or whatever sounds like fun!
Please give a warm welcome
to Mayonaka Punch!!
Yay!
Then edit the photo taken
separately from the video,
The Late-Night
Girls' Talk
Begins!!
and there's your thumbnail!
Upload videos
Once you have everything ready,
upload your video and give it a title.
MayoPan Intro
Fill in the description, tags,
and everything else.
It's finally ready to go!
Are you okay not being on camera?
Breaking: Masakichi fired
Fifth Champion Tanaka: The latest videos were awful.
Are you two okay?
It's me, Hana: Masakichi's out, huh? Makes sense
stinger @chikchik_m3k
She wasn't the one I punched, so what's her deal?
Stop playing the victim... So annoying
stinger @chikchik_m3k
You seriously can't even do this? So useless
gun666: Show yourself, Masakichi
Eye Drops: Go away loser
bom777: ggwp
Ma: Why are you two apologizing?
tasteless odorless: You might be better off
going your separate ways.
It's fine.
But...
Oh, you know!
If I showed my face,
that Yuki lady might call you out
for associating with a human again.
So I'll stay on the production side instead.
Sure...
Okay, are you ready?
Time to upload Mayonaka Punch's
very first video.
It probably won't be like back then.
Not a lot of people will notice us.
But now, I can start fresh.
This time, I'm not alone!
Publish video!
The Chu-Chu Girls. Have Started a New Late-Night Girls' Talk Channel!!
And so, we'll give it all we've got!
So please subscribe
to our channel and leave a like!
Thank you!
Ichiko
Sent you a sticker
Goodnight
Ichiko!
And Fu!
Mannaka Punch has finally started!
Mayonaka Punch...
Mannaka Punch!
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm fighting my own alter ego!
Shadowboxing?
Next time: "A New Member Joins! DEAD or ALIVE"!
A New Member Joins! DEAD or ALIVE